(this["webpackJsonptrivia-react"]=this["webpackJsonptrivia-react"]||[]).push([[0],{13:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(21)},20:function(e,t,a){},21:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var s=a(0),n=a.n(s),c=a(10),i=a.n(c),o=function(){var e=(new Date).getFullYear();return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement("footer",null,"\xa9 ",e," Oscar Villalta"))},r=function(){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"header"},n.a.createElement("h1",null,"Weird Trivia Fun"))},u=a(23),l=a(2),h=function(e){var t=e.answers,a=e.handleClick,s=Object(l.shuffle)(t)||[];return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,s.map((function(e){return n.a.createElement(u.a,{key:e.choice,onClick:function(e){return a(e)}},e.choice)})))},m=a(22),f=function(e){var t=e.question;return n.a.createElement(n.a.Fragment,null,n.a.createElement(m.a,null,n.a.createElement("h2",null,t)))},d=a(7),w=a(4),g=function e(){var t=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:{};Object(w.a)(this,e),this.choice="",this.status=!1,Object.assign(this,t)},k=function e(){var t=arguments.length>0&&void 0!==arguments[0]?arguments[0]:{};Object(w.a)(this,e),this.question="",this.answers=[],Object.assign(this,t)},p=a(12),v=[{question:"If a person holds 3 widgets, How many tires can fit in a locker?",answers:[{choice:"Banana",status:!0},{choice:"Dirt",status:!1},{choice:"Umbrella",status:!1},{choice:"Square root of a triangle",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"If a plane is going 300mph, does Puppy like gyros?",answers:[{choice:"James Cameron",status:!0},{choice:"Martian",status:!1},{choice:"Guitar",status:!1},{choice:"Javascript",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"10 times 6 is...",answers:[{choice:"Car",status:!0},{choice:"George Washington",status:!1},{choice:"Perpetual Motion",status:!1},{choice:"Tower of Hanoi",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"The seven dwarfs are part of which highway",answers:[{choice:"Hans Christian Anderson",status:!0},{choice:"Hamster",status:!1},{choice:"17 USD",status:!1},{choice:"Aorta",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Dallas, Massachussets is adjacent to the cellular membrane on which sandwich?",answers:[{choice:"Salacious Crumb",status:!0},{choice:"Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis",status:!1},{choice:"6 of Diamonds",status:!1},{choice:"Twelveteen",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Udo has a grain of salt. There are many wolves in a hectare.  Is rose the color of a prodigy?",answers:[{choice:"Truffles",status:!0},{choice:"Axe Body Spray",status:!1},{choice:"C",status:!1},{choice:"Vincent Van Gogh",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Actor, inanimate carbon rod, stars in which Sci-Fi potato?",answers:[{choice:"Yardstick",status:!0},{choice:"Blue",status:!1},{choice:"February 14th 2008",status:!1},{choice:"Chicago Bulls",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"A crystalline solution of ketchup is also known as...",answers:[{choice:"External Occipital Protubrance",status:!0},{choice:"Edgar Allen Poe",status:!1},{choice:"Horse",status:!1},{choice:"Ceiling Fan",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Where is the tallest amoeba in a walnut located.",answers:[{choice:"Roast Beef Sandwich",status:!0},{choice:"Labor Pains",status:!1},{choice:"Jaundice",status:!1},{choice:"A-10 Thunderbolt",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"During the War of 485, cosmonauts invented which Tetris Game?",answers:[{choice:"Astral Projection",status:!0},{choice:"Lightning and Thunder",status:!1},{choice:"NORAD",status:!1},{choice:"Isildur",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Human Centipedes are most commonly used for this type of degenerative tissue behavior.",answers:[{choice:"10,000 Maniacs",status:!0},{choice:"Speed of Sound",status:!1},{choice:"Array of Objects",status:!1},{choice:"a battery",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"},{question:"Peanut butter and waffled french fries, sometimes, are referred to this type of oil change",answers:[{choice:"The Quickening",status:!0},{choice:"UMDNJ",status:!1},{choice:"United Airlines",status:!1},{choice:"Grover Cleveland",status:!1}],link:"somelink.com"}],b=new(function(){function e(){Object(w.a)(this,e)}return Object(p.a)(e,[{key:"get",value:function(){var e=v.map((function(e){return new k(e)}));return Object(l.shuffle)(e)}}]),e}()),E=function(){var e=function(){var e=Object(s.useState)([new k]),t=Object(d.a)(e,2),a=t[0],n=t[1],c=Object(s.useState)(!1),i=Object(d.a)(c,2),o=i[0],r=i[1],u=Object(s.useState)(0),h=Object(d.a)(u,2),m=h[0],f=h[1],w=a[m].answers,p=Object(l.find)(w,(function(e){return e.status}))||new g;Object(s.useEffect)((function(){m!==a.length-1||r(!1)}),[m,a]);return{gameIsOn:o,currentQuestionId:m,startGame:function(){n(b.get()),f(0),r(!0)},handleClick:function(e){e.currentTarget.textContent!==p.choice?console.log("choose again..."):f(m+1)},questions:a}}(),t=e.currentQuestionId,a=e.handleClick,c=e.gameIsOn,i=e.startGame,o=e.questions[t];return c?n.a.createElement("div",{className:"game"},n.a.createElement("div",{className:"question-wrapper"},n.a.createElement(f,{question:o.question})),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"answer-wrapper"},n.a.createElement(h,{answers:o.answers,handleClick:a}))):n.a.createElement("div",{className:"game start-page"},n.a.createElement(u.a,{onClick:i},"Start Game"))},O=function(){return n.a.createElement(E,null)},q=function(){return n.a.createElement("div",{className:"app"},n.a.createElement(r,null),n.a.createElement("div",{className:"main"},n.a.createElement(O,null)),n.a.createElement(o,null))};a(20);i.a.render(n.a.createElement(n.a.StrictMode,null,n.a.createElement(q,null)),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[13,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.ecf52e34.chunk.js.map